Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
JACK KING: (ON RADIO)
T-minus 15 seconds.
Guidance is internal.
12, 11, 10, 9...
Ignition sequence starts.
6, 5, 4,
3, 2, 1...
Zero. All engines running.
Liftoff.
We have liftoff on Apollo 11.
NEIL ARMSTRONG:
Fuel and oxygen steady.
Cabin holding. Power is good.
Altitude is four miles now.
Velocity, 2,195 feet
per second.
BUZZ ALDRIN: Good radar data.
Altitude now, 33,500 feet.
How are you looking?
All your systems go.
KING: They're a go.
Hang tight.
You're a go
to continue power descent.
ARMSTRONG: Uh, Houston,
I'm getting
a little fluctuation.
CHARLIE DUKE: And, Eagle, Houston,
we got data drop-outs.
ALDRIN: Three feet down,
two and a half.
Picking up some dust.
ARMSTRONG: Okay. Engine stop.
(ECHOING)
The Eagle has landed.
(LOW RUMBLING)
(AFRICA BY TOTO PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
♪ "Hurry, boy,
it's waiting there for you"
♪ It's gonna take a lot
to drag me away from you
♪ There's nothing
that a hundred men or more
♪ Could ever do
♪ I bless the rains
down in Africa
♪ Gonna take some time to do
the things we never had... ♪
What does it even mean
to "miss the rains
down in Africa"?
The lyrics are
"I bless the rains
down in Africa."
What? No, they're not.
FOWLER: Uh, yes, they are.
BRIAN: It makes
even less sense.
Well, I should know,
because I karaoke'd it
at my wedding.
BRIAN: Ah. Well,
I must have missed that.
I was in the zone.
Tearing it up
on the dance floor.
(CHUCKLES) You can't dance
to save your life.
Anyone ever tell you guys
you bicker like
an old married couple?
That's 'cause
she's my work wife.
- Back to work, rookie.
- (AFRICA CONTINUES PLAYING)
(SINGING ALONG)
♪ ...could ever do
♪ I miss the rain
down in Africa ♪
I would like to thank you
for spending your honeymoon
in space with us.
It was either space or Italy.
But Italy
doesn't beat this view.
BRIAN: (SINGING OFF-KEY)
♪ I miss the rains
♪ Down in Africa
- Brian. Oh, my God.
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
BRIAN: (BREAKING UP) ♪ I miss
the rains down in Africa ♪
(ALARMS BLARING)
(BRIAN VOCALIZING)
What the hell is that?
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
- (FOWLER GRUNTS)
- (ALARMS BLARING)
(GASPS)
MARCUS: Brian!
- Marcus!
- MARCUS: Help me.
I'm losing air.
Brian!
(STRAINING)
(BOTH YELP)
(GASPS FOR AIR)
- Jo. Fowler, come in.
- MARCUS: Help me.
BRIAN: Marcus!
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Oh, God.
Okay, hang on.
- Marcus. Marcus, come in.
- (RADIO STATIC)
- Marcus.
Marcus.
God damn it.
(VALVE HISSES)
(WHIRRING)
(GRUNTS)
Come on.
- Come on.
- (VALVE HISSES)
- (METAL CREAKS)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
No. Marcus...
No.
(SIGHS)
I'm gonna get you home.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
NEWSCASTER: (ON TV)
Our viewers might remember
the accident that happened
during a routine satellite
repair mission 18 months ago.
Today, a D.C. court of appeals
handed down
the final judgement
on ex-astronaut
Brian Harper's
wrongful termination suit
against NASA,
his former employer.
We have obtained footage
of an internal NASA debriefing
where Harper claimed
that the accident
was caused by a mysterious
technological space anomaly.
So, this so-called "swarm"
hit the shuttle?
Yes, for the 50th time.
It impacted
in the Mare Crisium.
HUTCHINGS: Commander Fowler,
a passing meteor
or a solar flare
could have caused that kind
of disturbance, correct?
FOWLER: As you know,
I was unconscious, but...
HUTCHINGS: Yes or no?
Can a solar flare
cause the kind of disturbance
you witnessed
in the shuttle's
onboard system?
I guess, yes, technically.
It could have.
BRIAN: Are you kidding me?
I lost my friend up there.
HUTCHINGS:
Because of negligence.
NEWSCASTER:
Harper was once celebrated
for his heroic landing
of the Endeavour space shuttle
in spite of
a complete meltdown
of all onboard electronics.
Harper's legal options
have been exhausted
and it's become clear
that the accident
was the result of human error.
Today's loss is the final blow
in this very public
fall from grace.
BRENDA: Hey, Sonny.
Do you need
to be watching that again?
You know what?
Grandma is going to be
so excited to see you.
Dad's not coming, is he?
Your dad's got a lot
going on right now.
I know. That's why
we lost the house.
Maybe he'll come visit you
for Thanksgiving.
Would you like that?
I don't wanna move.
I hate New Jersey.
(PANTING)
I'm sorry, sir.
My mum always said
"it's better to beg
for forgiveness
"than ask permission."
(LINE RINGING)
Oh, crap.
Was that red or blue?
Please tell me it was blue.
MAN: (ON PHONE) Observatorio
Nacional de Chile.
- Esteban?
- ESTEBAN: Si?
- It's Professor Arrowood.
- ESTEBAN: Ah!
I see you're logging in
to our telescope, Professor.
Oh, yeah. I'm still tracking
our Moon's orbit.
Would you mind
sending last night's scans?
Use the other e-mail
I gave you though,
not the school one.
- ESTEBAN: Like always, sir.
- (DOOR OPENS)
(WOMAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(CLEARS THROAT) Gotta run.
Um, uh...
- Ciao.
- ESTEBAN: Adios.
Hola senoras.
Hola.
(VEHICLE HORN HONKS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(VAN DOOR SHUTS)
You're seven
and a half minutes late.
I have to write this up.
- Hello, there.
- Hi.
What can I get you?
I'd like a Pastrami Madness...
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
...and I would also
like to ask you, dear,
what sauces do you serve
with the pastrami?
Oh, yeah. We've got barbecue,
honey mustard, ranch...
What the fuck!
What was the... the last one?
One Madness coming up.
We have a strict
no phone policy.
Can I take my 10?
(LINE RINGING)
Hello. My name
is Dr. KC Houseman,
and I've uncovered
what might be
the most important discovery
in human history.
I need you to patch me through
to the director of NASA
immediately.
Honey, I sell T-shirts
and toys.
I can patch you through
to customer service.
Please hold.
(MUZAK PLAYING ON PHONE)
- (PHONE BEEPS)
- (SIGHS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
(DOOR SQUEAKING)
Black, two sugar.
Oh, you read my mind.
Thank you.
What are you doing up
so early?
I could ask you the same.
Is everything okay?
Will be.
So I'm gonna be home by dinner.
If I'm not,
make sure Jimmy does his homework,
- has a bath...
- You worry too much.
I've got everything
under control.
Right. Talk soon.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(BUSY CHATTER)
- (CHATTER DIES DOWN)
- (FOWLER PANTING)
Okay, don't everybody
speak at once.
The Moon's orbit
has shifted.
I'm sorry.
Its orbital radius
is decreasing.
Well, that's not possible.
We thought the same,
so we ran the numbers
and triple-checked our data.
So, the Moon's been
orbiting around the Earth
for billions of years,
and now you're telling me
it's changed its course?
(JOHANSEN CLEARS THROAT)
This isn't kindergarten,
speak.
Right, uh, yes.
So, on its last orbit,
our Lunar Reconnaissance Probe
picked up something strange.
FOWLER: What is that?
We don't know.
We have
photometric measurements
of gaseous spectra
being emitted from inside.
Where is this?
JOHANSEN: Mare Crisium.
KC: How many times
do I have to tell you?
I need to speak
to Deputy Director Fowler
immediately.
But this is urgent.
I understand how
a restraining order works,
but if you people at NASA
won't listen to me,
how am I supposed to...
Hello?
(PANTING)
What would Elon do?
(CAT MEOWS)
Oh, Fuzz Aldrin.
How many times have I told you
to use the litter box?
(FUZZ MEOWS)
Oh, God.
"Astronaut Day."
This is today.
Fuzz, you're a damn genius!
Extra back scratches later.
(BRAKES SCREECH)
(DOOR HINGES CREAK)
- (PANTING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Our teacher said you're
a washed up no-show.
She's complaining to someone.
You really don't look
like an astronaut.
Well, are you going to
teach us about space or what?
MAN: Brian!
- (BRIAN INHALES SHARPLY)
- Brian!
- (SIGHS)
- (BANGING ON DOOR)
Open the goddamn door.
You're three months late!
Shit.
I can hear you in there.
- Oh, shit. Oof!
- Brian!
(ENGINE ROARS)
KC: To put it bluntly,
the Moon is a megastructure.
Do you get it?
Huge and artificial!
Whoever built
this incredible thing
must think
we're a pathetic species.
But don't even get me
started on eclipses.
They're only possible
because the Moon
is exactly 400 times smaller
than the Sun,
and exactly 400 times
closer to the Earth.
Anyone know how that happened?
Uh... 'Cause the Moon's
a megastructure?
Yeah, someone's
paying attention!
Let me tell you kids
something.
When Apollo 12 dropped
their empty fuel tank,
the impact made the Moon
ring like a bell.
- Bong!
- (CHILDREN GASP)
It rang for hours.
And do you know why?
Because the damn Moon
is hollow.
Put that in your pipe
and smoke it.
(PANTING)
Hello. I'm Brian Harper.
I'm supposed to be
speaking here today.
BOY: Oh!
I'm Dr. KC Houseman,
megastructurist.
It's a real honor.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Um...
I've made
a shocking discovery.
I need you to get me in
touch with NASA immediately.
Well, NASA and I aren't really
on speaking terms these days.
Well, that will change...
when you tell them that
the Moon is out of orbit.
Really?
Hey, kids, I'm gonna
go get this all sorted out.
Be right back.
Look at the data.
A natural body does not
change its orbit overnight.
Yeah, well, my natural body
is walking away
from you right now.
There must be something wrong
with the Moon's power source.
- Yeah, that must be it.
- I knew you'd believe me.
People usually think
I'm some kind of crackpot.
Hey, fellas, I need this guy
escorted off the premises
for impersonating me
and creeping out
a bunch of school kids.
I was not
impersonating you.
Sir, I'm going to have
to ask you to come with us.
Sorry, man.
I got enough on my plate without
some crazy guy thinking
the Moon's out of orbit.
- I'm not crazy!
- Okay.
Read this.
All right, I'm on my way.
(BRIAN SIGHS)
Oh. Hi.
(SOFT INDIE ROCK SONG
PLAYING ON STEREO)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Is this a butt dial?
Put on channel 16.
BRIAN: Well, I thought
we weren't speaking anymore.
Are you watching?
REPORTER: The two suspects
who have rolled through
at least two red lights...
Okay, looks like some idiot
tried to outrun the cops.
Yeah. That idiot is your son.
Sonny doesn't even have a car.
I'm still fixing up
the Mustang.
(SIGHS) Tom gave him one
for his birthday.
REPORTER: The car has stopped.
It's an expensive sports car.
Two young men that appear
to be in their 20s.
Oh, my God.
Are you seeing this?
REPORTER:
LAPD have them in custody.
Out for a joy ride
and this day is not going
to end well for them.
NEWSCASTER: There you have it.
Another high-speed
car chase...
(BRIAN SIGHS)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
BAILIFF: Next case,
Sonny Neil Harper.
(HANDCUFFS OPEN)
It says here
you just turned 18.
Unfortunately,
that makes you an adult
in the eyes of the law.
What? Hey, aren't you
gonna say something?
Because of the reckless nature
of your actions
and the amount
of illegal substances
present at the time
of your arrest...
No, Your Honor.
Those drugs weren't his.
They were just his buddy's.
They were on their way
- to a concert.
- Quiet in my court.
Well, he just got scared.
That's why he took off.
All right, that's it.
Bailiff.
Your Honor, excuse the actions
of my client's father.
We're prepared to pay
whatever the bail is
right now.
Money's no object.
Well, I guess that makes
the defendant a flight risk.
Your Honor, we do not mean
to offend the court
in any way.
I'm postponing this
bail hearing till next week.
(GAVEL BANGS)
Bailiff, remove Mr. Harper.
Wait. You can't...
Don't listen to him.
You can't put him in jail
for a week.
Please, I'm begging you.
Sonny, I'm gonna get you out.
If you're looking
for the deal of your life,
come to Tom Lopez Lexus,
where you're not
just a customer,
we treat you like family.
Do you have any idea
how a courtroom operates?
Your lawyer was doing nothing.
Oh, so you know better
than my lawyer
who's on a $50,000 retainer!
I thought money
was no object, Tom.
Oh, no, no, no.
It is when you don't have any.
BRIAN: Nice move, by the way.
Sonny's now a flight risk.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
This guy's unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
All right, everyone,
just cool it.
- Now, what the hell happened?
- TOM: Oh, what happened?
When Brian had to open
his big mouth,
he had a little speech.
Oh, my God. Go to hell, Tom.
Yeah, you know what?
And you go to outer space,
- far away from us.
- BRENDA: Guys!
We're all just trying
to help Sonny right here.
Oh, wait, Brian's trying
to help Sonny? Since when?
Brenda, honestly, what do you
see in this schmuck?
Oh, you're a big man,
aren't you?
How did this happen?
Why wasn't he at USC?
He moved out when you
got him that new apartment.
So ask him.
He barely returns
my calls anymore.
Welcome to the club.
(SIGHS)
(CALL ENDS)
(INDISTINCT TV CHATTER)
Oh, KC, is that you?
Hey, Mum.
Rosmarinus officinalis.
A few studies have found
that smelling rosemary
can improve
your short-term memory.
Oh, that's lovely, dear.
Thank you.
(CHUCKLES) Thank you.
Oh, no, no, no, Mum.
Let me do that.
There we go.
So, how are you feeling?
Great.
But enough about me.
Everybody here knows
that my son is a genius
working at NASA.
What?
I'm a nobody, Mum.
Well, you're somebody to me.
I actually did make
a discovery.
But it doesn't matter.
No one will listen to me.
Then make them.
Make them listen?
Oh, hello.
Are you new here?
No, Mum.
It's me. It's KC.
Your son.
HUTCHINGS: Can someone tell me
what the hell I'm looking at?
The Moon has entered
an elliptical orbit.
Meaning?
MAN 1: It'll circle
around us three times
before it reaches
the Roche Limit
at 17,000 kilometers.
At that point, city-sized
pieces of Moon debris
will rain down on us.
HUTCHINGS:
So we have three months?
MAN 2: Not exactly.
As the Moon
moves closer to us,
our months
will begin to shorten.
We've estimated a timeline
of roughly three weeks.
Maybe less than that.
We have some new high-res
scans that just came in.
Jesus Christ.
Is that a hole
in the crater floor?
So what are our options here?
We have to go back
to the Moon.
We have to see
what's going on up there.
How do we carry crew?
I've already talked
to my contacts in Europe.
We can potentially
get a STC-62
en route by tomorrow.
HUTCHINGS: Potentially?
Great.
I'll just brief the president
on a maybe.
In the meantime, everyone
keep your mouths shut.
(CELL PHONES CHIMING)
MAN 2: Um...
That might be a problem.
It's, uh, trending on Twitter
as of two minutes ago.
It's your ex-husband.
FOWLER: Thank you.
Hey, Doug, I'm a little busy
right now. What is it?
DOUG: (ON PHONE) Is it true?
Tell me there's been
some kind of mistake.
(SIGHS) I wish I could,
but the math
actually checks out.
So, it's happening.
How's Jimmy?
Well, you'd know if you
saw him once in a while.
Please don't start.
I call him all the time.
Sorry, I gotta run.
Oh...
- Your Honor.
- Jesus Christ!
I guess hanging up
wasn't clear enough.
I just need two minutes
of your time.
You have
till I reach the door.
I got a classic bike
and my son's vintage Mustang
that I can use as collateral
till I get money,
whatever you need.
Are you trying to bribe me?
In a courthouse?
I just wanna get my son back.
The courts are closed.
- Will they reopen Monday?
- (SCOFFS)
Not likely.
What's that supposed to mean?
Look, I'm just trying
to get the heck outta here
before the traffic
becomes a nightmare.
- I suggest you do the same.
- NEWSCASTER: Breaking news.
We go now live
to the NASA press briefing
to discuss the Moon
being out of orbit.
REPORTER: Astronomers
have noticed bright lights
on the lunar surface lately.
Do you know the identity
of the anonymous source?
- (REPORTERS ON TV CLAMORING)
- HUTCHINGS: Everyone, please.
We're confident that
the lunar recon mission
will provide
the necessary data
to address the problem.
There's no need to panic.
That's all for now.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
You just lied
to the whole country.
HUTCHINGS: Get in line,
you work for me.
I work for
the American people,
and you're keeping them
in the dark.
Yeah.
SCIENTIST: (ON TV) NASA is
completely downplaying this.
Imagine the tides
on the coast...
(PHONE RINGING)
...growing hundreds
of times larger,
moving hundreds
of miles inland,
then you'll get an idea
of what we're in for.
NEWSCASTER: Some of
your harshest critics claim
- that you're exaggerating...
- TOM: Hey.
All flights to the West Coast
have been cancelled.
And I'm stuck in traffic.
TOM: Oh, I'm so sorry.
SCIENTIST:
Moving to higher ground
it's the only possible chance
of surviving this.
Honey. We should go to Aspen.
What about Sonny?
We can't just leave him there.
TOM: No, no, no.
We're not gonna leave him.
The lawyer's
gonna get him out
the moment the judge
sets bail.
And I'll find a way
to get him to Colorado.
We're going to Colorado?
No. No, Tom.
SCIENTIST:
Earth's stronger gravity
will completely break
the Moon apart
and send thousands
of mile-sized chunks
raining down upon the planet.
Okay, okay, okay. Hey, Google.
Turn off the TV.
Girls, go pack.
GOOGLE: Turning the TV off.
TOM: Girls, go pack
your snow boots.
Come on. Hurry up.
We have to start thinking
about the girls.
And trust me,
we are not gonna
forget about Sonny.
MAN: (ON RADIO)
T-minus five seconds.
Four, three,
two, one.
Ignition.
REPORTER 1: This is it.
The entire world is holding
its collective breath
as the joint missions
between NASA
and the European
Space Agencies
take to the skies today.
REPORTER 2:
Nations remain hopeful
of NASA's lunar mission
as frantic shoppers continue
to stockpile supplies
as mounting Moon terror fuels
the mass migration
out of metropolitan areas.
NEWSCASTER 1: Civilization
has already taken
a serious nosedive.
Looting has become
a favorite pastime
in the United Kingdom.
REPORTER 3: Fear and
panic have overtaken our city.
The National Guard struggles
to restore some kind of order.
MAN: Stay awake,
my brothers and sisters.
As the stars fall from Heaven,
stay awake!
REPORTER 4:
These armed religious fanatics
have racked up
thousands of followers
all over the country.
- (GRUNTS)
- (TOOL CLATTERS)
REPORTER 5: In other news,
prominent scientists
are now exploring
the possibility
that perhaps
the Moon could be
some sort of
orbital megastructure.
A term first popularized
by fringe astronomers,
megastructures describe
artificial
planet-sized objects
said to be powered
by captured stars.
This once radical possibility
is now gaining traction
among a scientific community
desperate for answers.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
Come out! Hands up!
Easy, easy.
You're that astronaut guy
from the other day.
I accidentally threw away
some very important papers.
Lucky for you, sanitation
hasn't come by all week.
Yeah, it's, uh, lucky for me.
"Orbital distance"?
- Are you looking for this?
- (PANTING)
KC: My fellow
megastructurists,
if you're watching this,
then you know by now
a huge problem
is heading our way,
and we're the only ones
who can solve it.
An emergency meeting
is being called,
our usual place immediately.
L.A. Palm Hotel. Today. 1800.
Free bagels.
(EPIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Lunar orbit insertion
complete.
Houston, we're approaching
the Mare Crisium.
Initiating capsule rotation.
Affirmative.
15 degrees. 30.
45. 70. 90.
COMMANDER: STC-62 in position.
Houston, you seeing this?
FOWLER: Copy, we see it.
Prepare to deploy the probe.
Affirmative.
Releasing probe.
Stand by for stage two.
MOSLEY: Dropping steadily.
KC: (ON MIC) I posted
on every platform.
Why don't those idiots at NASA
see the real problem?
Because they obviously
haven't read
famed cosmologist
Carl Sagan's work,
where he clearly states
that a natural satellite
cannot be a hollow object.
I... I've been saying that
for years, Dr. Houseman.
That doesn't help us now,
does it, Ziggy?
This room is full
of the smartest
and most visionary people
in the world.
(COUGHS)
KC: We all know the Moon's
a constructed object. Okay?
There has to be a way
to fix it.
Come on, people,
think outside the box.
Oswald did it.
Oh, damn it, Gary. Not now.
Mr. Harper.
What are you doing here?
Probably making
a huge mistake.
Can we talk?
How did you know I was here?
Your website.
You read my blog?
You knew all this was
happening before anyone.
Before NASA. How?
Why bother?
You're just gonna say
I'm crazy again.
Try me.
Well, for years I've been
studying distant planets,
searching for one of
these orbiting megastructures.
But I never could
have imagined
there'd be one right here,
in our own backyard.
Ever heard of a Dyson sphere?
Yeah.
Every megastructure
has a rigid shell
built around a power core.
Most likely
a captured white dwarf
that's being harnessed
for energy.
Something obviously happened
to the one inside our Moon
and that's why
it's veering off course.
Yeah, still crazy.
Why did you come here
if you're not going
to believe me?
'Cause I know what it's like
to try to tell
people something
and have no one listen.
MOSLEY: Probe depth
has reached 24.5 kilometers.
25 kilometers.
Holding steady
at 25.6 kilometers.
Still holding.
- It stopped?
- It's coming back.
24 kilometers.
20.
15.
We got another problem.
The Moon's orbit
is shifting again.
What?
It's correcting itself.
- (ALARMS BLARING)
- Uh, Houston,
we're experiencing
some kind of malfunction.
Houston, do you copy?
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
- (ALARM BEEPS)
- Hull breach. Helmets.
(GRUNTS)
(SHRIEKING)
(MALE ASTRONAUT 1 SCREAMING)
(MALE ASTRONAUT 2 SCREAMING)
(STATIC)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING)
REPORTER: (ON TV)
In breaking news,
NASA has just corrected
- their initial projection...
- (LIGHTER FLICKING)
...of the Moon's path
over Earth.
(SKA MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES)
The governor
has just ordered
the mass evacuation
of the entire West Coast,
recommending that people
urgently head
to higher ground.
As the Moon
keeps closing in on Earth
in a chaotic,
and as one scientist put it...
(BURSTING IN DISTANCE)
Guys! (PANTING)
The... The...
The tide, it's coming.
Come on.
We gotta get outta here.
KC: Wait!
Everybody, upstairs. Go!
Everybody, get up!
Come on! Go, go!
KC, what are you doing?
- KC!
- (KC YELPS)
(KC YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
KC, hang on!
(KC GASPING)
(KC WHIMPERS)
I can't swim!
Dr. Houseman!
Hang on!
(YELPS)
(KC GASPING)
He's right there.
Hang on!
(BRIAN GRUNTING)
- (KC GRUNTING)
- Come on!
Come on.
BRIAN: Come on.
(KC PANTING)
(COUGHING)
(SHRIEKING)
It's some kind of self-aware,
self-replicating singularity.
Like a machine?
Machines don't have
intelligence. This does.
It's everything
we feared about A.I.
And it knew we were coming.
So it was probably drawn out
by the electronic signature
of the capsule.
Everything
we thought we knew
about the nature
of the universe
has just
gone out the window.
We're not prepared for this.
Deb, don't argue, just pack
your stuff. We're leaving.
So you're just gonna quit?
What do you want me to do?
I want you to help us
figure out what
the hell this thing is,
so we can beat it.
We're not equipped for that.
You've seen
what we're up against.
You've been gunning for my job
for a while, Fowler.
Congrats, it's yours.
What are you not telling me?
You've got Q clearance.
The hole is
in the Mare Crisium.
That's what the Harper
hearings were all about.
If you're serious about going
down the NASA rabbit hole,
you should pay a visit
to Holdenfield.
Here's your clearance.
(SOFT CLASSICAL MUSIC
PLAYING ON SPEAKER)
(MONITOR BEEPING)
CLERK: How did you
get down here?
FOWLER: Hutchings
gave me this.
I'll need all records
of STX-136A.
- You waiting for something?
- (GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(KEYBOARD CLACKS)
- (AFRICA BY TOTO PLAYING)
- (BRIAN VOCALIZING)
MARCUS: What the hell is that?
I feel it.
MAN: What are you doing?
Holdenfield?
You're not supposed
to have that, 136 Alpha.
That's classified. Top secret.
Why is NASA
lying about all this?
July 20th, 1969.
"One small step for man,
"one giant leap for..."
yada, yada, yada.
In school,
you were taught that Apollo 11
lost contact
with Mission Control
for two minutes. Not true.
Mission Control
cut their feed to the world
because they found something
on that day.
Strange pulsating lights
emanating from beneath
the Moon's crust.
It was me who was assigned
to keep it under wraps.
The Apollo crew played ball.
Everybody after.
Just Brian Harper wouldn't.
They called him crazy.
Threw him out with the trash.
You're telling me
that the Moon
was effectively the biggest
cover-up in human history?
(LAUGHING)
Biggest? Probably.
You had blood
on your hands, too.
Yeah, well,
anyone who follows orders
pretty much always does,
don't they?
That technology,
it's light years ahead of us.
Compared to that,
we're the Stone Age.
The only shot we had
to stop it
was Zulu X-Ray 7.
It was shut down. Shelved.
For budgetary reasons.
Well, Commander,
I have pressing business
waiting for me on my desk.
The sand in the hourglass
is dropping quickly
for all of us.
It's as good as gone.
I'm really sorry.
- (SWITCH CLICKS)
- Really.
- (DISCONNECT TONE)
- (BRIAN SIGHS)
(SOFTLY) Damn it.
KC: What's wrong?
I can't reach my son.
Uh...
Word is, um,
you're an astronaut,
so you must know that
the entire inside
of the Moon
is full of produce.
KC, can you tell
Birkenstocks here
that I'm dangerously close
to hurling him out a window?
Okay, well,
let's find an empty room.
ZIGGY: How do you think
the Incas got their potatoes?
Sorry.
You said that if we can
destroy this thing...
FOWLER: We have a theory
that the Moon might return
to its original orbit.
And how do you propose
we do that exactly?
You said so yourself,
using a modern spacecraft
is not feasible.
I am working on a solution.
GENERAL JENKINS:
We appreciate your effort,
but this is now
a military operation.
We'll take it from here.
Doug! Wait!
If you launch nukes,
the global fallout
is gonna kill everybody.
Who said anything about nukes?
You are making
a big mistake here.
Please,
let me put together a plan.
We have a plan.
(SIGHS)
Look, why don't you and Jimmy
come with me to Colorado?
You'll be safe there.
What are you asking me to do?
Quit? Give up?
I'm asking you
to think about our son.
I am thinking about our son.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(DISCONNECT TONE)
KC: Where is he?
Uh, jail.
He's a good kid,
just made a mistake.
I was always
doing stupid things.
Don't know how my parents
put up with me.
We never had a lot of money,
but sometimes
we'd all get fish 'n chips,
sit out on the dock
and just watch the stars
for hours.
(CHUCKLES)
That was when I first dreamed
of being an astronaut.
After my father passed,
my mum wanted to move
back to the States.
My dad laughed when I told him
I wanted to be an astronaut.
Didn't believe in you?
Oh, that's putting it lightly.
I worked my ass off
to get into NASA.
I read all about
your last mission.
You saw alien tech.
And NASA insisted
it was a meteor.
But it wasn't?
It was unlike anything
I'd ever seen.
And, you know,
the worst part
is I lost a friend up there.
And it was my fault.
Oh, come on.
How was it your fault?
You saved the shuttle.
You saved Fowler.
A lot of good that did.
I'm divorced, broke,
my son hates me.
God, I am so jealous.
Alien tech. (CHUCKLES)
It's freakin' awesome.
(SCOFFS)
REPORTER: Extreme weather
is hammering
the Eastern Seaboard
and Gulf Coast
with high tides and flooding
wreaking havoc
on residents and properties.
Folks, if you aren't
already on high ground,
you better get there
as soon as possible.
MICHELLE: Um,
as an exchange student,
are you sure they're going
to let me into the bunker?
Yeah. Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you.
REPORTER: ...and loss of life
in populated areas.
As you can see, the images
coming out of Bangladesh
- are simply horrific
- Mom, are we gonna die?
No. No, sweetheart.
I know all of this
that's happening
seems so scary,
but we are not
gonna die. Okay?
We're all gonna be safe
with Dad in Colorado.
Are you sending more
rockets to the Moon?
No. No. You know why?
Because we don't...
we don't have
any more of these.
Why not?
Because they're all
in museums.
And, um...
Uh...
(WHISPERING)
I love you, sweetheart.
(PHONE RINGING)
- (PHONE BEEPS)
- FOWLER: (ON PHONE) Hey, Doug.
What is a ZX-7?
DOUG: Who told you about that?
FOWLER: Well, come on.
What is it?
(SIGHS) Zulu X-Ray Seven
was a prototype EMP device.
But the program got disbanded.
Okay, well, it's clear that
this thing inside the Moon
is technological
in nature, right?
I assume they thought an EMP
could take the thing out.
We don't have a way into space
so this is a moot point.
Okay, well, how far along
was the testing?
Jocinda, NASA isn't cleared
for another mission.
How about you let me
worry about that?
AUCLAIR: (ON COMMS)
GPS is locked on LZ.
Compensate latitude
by minus 4.5 west.
4.5 degrees. Copy.
Reducing to 10 knots.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(SOLDIER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
- AUCLAIR: Open the door.
- (SIGHS)
BRIAN: (GROANS) Yeah?
- AUCLAIR: Brian Harper?
- Yeah.
We need you to come with us.
It's a matter
of national security.
(SIGHS) All right.
Give me a second.
I'm not going anywhere
without him.
Yeah, we're a team.
(SIGHS)
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Sorry, I'm sorry, miss.
Sorry.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
(PANTING)
It's been nearly three hours.
That can't be a good sign.
What's with
all the pill popping?
You're really sweating
over there.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
(KC CONTINUES PANTING)
No. I broke into UC Irvine
multiple times.
I lost two of their mops.
They probably know.
Oh, you gotta be
kidding me. No.
Look, I don't want to be here
any more than you do.
- (BRIAN GROANS)
- Sit down.
No, no, no. I don't have to
take orders from you anymore.
I'm just curious, you still
screwing over your friends?
- Oh, you talking about me?
- How many of these
- wonderful people here...
- Really?
Guys!
Who the hell is this?
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Dr. KC Houseman, ma'am.
I wrote you several e-mails,
but you never responded.
What's this all about?
Follow me.
What you're about to see,
only a handful of people
have ever seen before.
KC knew the Moon
was out of orbit
before you guys did.
Social media went wild
when I posted my research.
You're the
"unidentified source"?
Oh, yes.
Oh, God.
Mosley, pull up
the tunnel, please.
(COMPUTER TRILLING)
Our readings
estimate its depth
to be over 25 kilometers.
BRIAN:
That's the Mare Crisium.
FOWLER: Exactly.
I think whatever happened
all those years ago
is directly responsible
for what's happening
right now.
Oh, so you believe me now?
I saw your helmet cam.
It's a little late
for an apology.
FOWLER:
We were both lied to.
The international mission
didn't just go sideways.
- (ASTRONAUT SCREAMING)
- It was attacked.
A technological life form.
No effin' way.
FOWLER: During the attack,
the Moon was attempting
to return
to its original orbit,
until this thing
went back inside the Moon.
This is what
I've been trying to tell you.
It's doing something to the
megastructure's power core.
Excuse me.
The megastructure?
Please don't ask.
It's highly likely our
Moon was built by aliens.
We have to get inside
and make first contact.
I told you not to ask.
All right, look,
we're planning a mission
to attack this thing.
The only problem is,
is it recognizes
our technology.
Which is why we need you.
Well, I never thought
I'd hear you say that again.
You're the only pilot
to ever land a shuttle
without power.
Not exactly a hirable skill.
Well, it is right now,
which is why I'm offering
you your job back,
and I'm personally
asking you for your help.
(WHISPERS)
Say yes, Brian.
I don't know.
I got a lot of my own
problems down here.
And the Moon
falling onto Earth
isn't one of them?
I was wrong to bring you here.
I am done.
How do you plan
on getting up there?
You know all of our shuttles
are in museums.
The Endeavour
is right here in L.A.
Plus, the Chinese are offering
their prototype moon lander.
I know it sounds
completely crazy.
No, no,
what you showed us was crazy.
This is a whole other
level of insane.
Ought to be right up
your alley then, no?
If I do this,
I'm gonna need
something in return.
Clear!
All clear over here.
Staircase on your left.
Keep your eyes open.
Did you reach him?
Yeah. It's being handled.
Sonny's gonna meet us
at Vandenberg.
BRIAN: Looks like
we missed the party.
I didn't even
get an invite.
FOWLER: At least somebody's
on the same page as us.
Hey, hey. Look what I found!
Maybe we can use it
as toilet paper.
- What?
- Take a look around you, man.
- It's worthless.
- Whatever. Let's go.
MAN: (ON LOUDSPEAKER)
Attention,
we are asking everyone
to please clear the streets
and to remain indoors...
(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
Dude, dude, we gotta
get outta here. Go!
(TIRES SCREECH)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Yeah. This is really,
really exciting, isn't it?
NEWSCASTER: As leaders
around the world
struggle for answers,
new images have surfaced
suggesting that NASA
might have plans
for a new lunar mission.
But so far, NASA
and the White House
have not responded
to requests for comment.
And this is just in
from our correspondent
in Southeast Asia.
Apparently, the Moon
is causing a drastic increase
in tectonic activity.
Reports of
countless earthquakes
and volcanic eruptions
keep pouring in.
That's weird.
What's weird?
The Moon doesn't have
enough gravity to do that,
no matter how close it gets.
You still don't get it.
We're dealing
with a megastructure.
Your rules
don't apply anymore.
FOWLER: We've been here
how long now,
and nobody's bothered
to paint over that?
It's kinda growing on me.
Hey, where's Sonny?
I sent a ground crew
to the prison, okay?
But I haven't heard anything
in a few days.
Why the hell
didn't you say that?
'Cause I need you
to be focused
on what's happening
right here.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
Megastructures
move through space
without an exhaust system.
The Moon has an engine?
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
Hold that thought.
I'll be right back.
Well, at least your husband
came through with that.
Ex-husband.
- Colonel.
- Director Fowler.
Commander Harper.
I'm Lieutenant Colonel Reed.
This is Captain Avery.
We've been briefed
by General Davidson.
AVERY: We need to walk you
through the arming procedure.
I'm an astronaut,
not a soldier.
I'll get you
where you need to go,
but I'm not setting off
any bomb.
We don't expect you to.
We'll accompany you
on the mission
and activate the device,
but you need to be familiar
with the process
should complications arise.
(AIR HISSES)
AVERY: The bomb's security
and authentication systems
have been removed.
Meaning we can arm it
without approval
from the ground.
Using a remote trigger.
Two clicks,
then push this down and hold.
Triggers the device to go off.
- Simple.
- Yeah. Simple.
Nearing Vandenberg, Captain.
Over.
Roger that.
Should've gotten you
the jumbo platter.
Thank you for getting me out.
You can thank your dad.
BRIAN: Plan is to take off
when the Moon
is closest to Earth.
Now, since we're dealing
with an unpredictable target,
navigation
is gonna be crucial.
Our navigator, Carl Saunders,
is gonna be making sure
we hit the mark,
flight engineer Hannah Martin
will run
real-time calculations
to ensure
that we intercept the Moon.
And once
we clear the atmosphere,
we'll begin
the refueling process.
Thankfully
our friends at SpaceX
have a propellant depot
currently in orbit.
I love Elon.
(CHUCKLES)
BRIAN: So once
we're all powered off,
we'll use our thrusters
to position ourselves
over the Mare Crisium.
Our Chinese friends
have jerry-rigged
the onboard systems
so that we can fly it
without electronics.
So we'll park the rover
section of the module
with the bomb inside,
then switch the electronics
back on
and use it as bait
to lure this thing
out of its hole.
Then, you guys
will pull the trigger
and kill it.
And then, hopefully,
we all can go back home.
If we still have one left.
What did I say?
Sonny. Oh, my God, son.
- Thank God you're okay.
- (MOUTHING) Thank you.
- Hold on.
- BRIAN: Okay.
Just so I'm clear,
you're gonna take
a bomb into space.
And why are you even here?
You hate NASA.
Just try to understand.
If there's even
the smallest chance
that this could work...
- What if it doesn't?
- It has to.
I want you to have a world
you can grow up in.
Where you can be
a better man than me.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Hey. (SIGHS)
DOUG: What have you seen
since you've been there?
JIMMY: (ON PHONE)
The space shuttle and stuff.
Do you miss me?
Yeah, I really miss you.
I miss you too, my little man.
Is Mom around?
Mom, it's Dad.
(IN MANDARIN)
FOWLER: (IN ENGLISH)
Wow, he's getting good.
Yeah?
I held up my end
of the bargain.
I want you and Jimmy
in Colorado.
We are. We're gonna be
airlifted out of here
as soon
as the shuttle launches.
Look, if anyone finds out
- what I've done for you...
- They won't.
You just make sure
your trigger-happy buddies
keep their hands
off the nukes.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Sorry, guys.
Out of two percent.
I looked everywhere.
Nah, this is great.
Thanks, man.
You know,
I almost got a job at NASA.
What department?
Janitorial.
(RUMBLING)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
(BOTH GRUNT)
MAN 1: Get out!
MAN 2: Hang on!
(THUD)
- (KC PANTING)
- (ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(OBJECT CLATTERS)
Is this your current
projected lunar orbit?
- Yeah.
- Why?
This obviously
isn't accounting
for the Moon's increased mass.
Look at
all this seismic activity
in the wake of its orbit.
We know
the Moon's surface gravity
is 1.62 meters squared.
At least it used to be.
So this must be wrong.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
ENGINEER:
I'm sorry, Director Fowler,
we have a problem.
Just what we need,
a damn earthquake.
We're losing coolant.
Well, there has to be
a way to fix it.
Not here. We would need
the entire team at Michoud
to rebuild
something like this.
Well, then get on the horn
and find somebody
who can help us.
Anyone that can help us
is already here.
Look,
we have to think about
letting all
of these people here
get to safety.
To safety?
These people here
won't have a planet
unless we figure
something out.
Brian, we're down an engine.
Launching is no longer
an option.
Thanks for bringing me here.
May I have
everyone's attention.
You've all done more
than we ever could have asked.
You have my deepest thanks
along with the thanks
of the entire country.
But it's now time
for you to go home.
I'm ordering
the immediate evacuation
of all personnel
from Vandenberg.
You'll meet up with
your families in Colorado.
SONNY: Dad.
I'm sorry it didn't work out.
Story of my life.
Thanks for getting me
out of jail.
Let's get our stuff.
It's time to go.
FOWLER: Time's up.
Chopper's ready.
Come on. Let's go.
(COMPUTERS BEEPING
AND TRILLING)
Go ahead.
I'll meet you out there.
Why are you guys still here?
Director Fowler,
when it comes back around,
the Moon's gravity will be
over 80% of the Earth's pull.
I know how it sounds,
but we checked
Dr. Houseman's data.
The numbers are solid.
Show the director
our new simulations.
We have to pull up
our launch window.
Guys, where have
you been? Look.
There is no launch window.
The mission's over.
(SYSTEM BEEPING SOFTLY)
Wait. Wait a minute.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
How do you feel
about flying the shuttle
with only two engines?
(HESITATES) It can't be done.
If we launch when the Moon
is directly above us,
the increased
gravitational pull
should give
the shuttle a boost,
giving you a really good
chance of getting into orbit.
You evacuated
my entire flight crew.
I can't fly the shuttle alone.
That's why I'm
going with you.
My guys will stay back
and handle the launch.
But we've got a very narrow
window of time here.
You'd have to be ready to go
in exactly 28 minutes.
You fly and I'll navigate.
Just like old times.
- What do you say?
- What about the EMP device?
It's still in the Moon Lander.
I mean, we lost the crew
so we're gonna have
to set it off ourselves,
but you paid attention, right?
KC: Two clicks, then press
the button down and hold.
Triggers the device
to go off. Simple.
You figured all this out?
FOWLER: And he calculated
our new launch trajectory.
You know, without electronics,
we're gonna need to make
split-second calculations
up there.
Plus, we lost
our flight engineer.
Mm.
No. No, no, no, guys.
I'm not cleared for this.
Well, I'm the
acting director of NASA,
so I just cleared you.
Congrats.
Yeah, but...
I've got IBS.
Irritable Bowel Syndrome.
- BRIAN: Mm.
- I get motion sickness, too.
You said you always wanted
to be an astronaut.
I have debilitating anxiety.
KC, if the Moon really
is what you think it is,
we're gonna need
a megastructurist.
Suit up.
(GASPING)
SOLDIER: That's great.
Let's move, move!
FOWLER: So, I've put your
dad's number in here, okay?
He knows you're coming.
I know I wasn't always easy.
That makes two of us.
You know this was
all your idea, right?
You're so smart.
But now,
I need you to be brave.
I don't want you to go.
I love you
(VOICE BREAKING) more than
all the stars in the sky.
Even more
than the whole Milky Way?
Way more.
(SIGHS)
Take good care of him.
Be safe up there.
BRIAN: Take this.
I hope you don't need it.
Stay off the main roads.
- Dad, I...
- Go.
Uh...
You do know
how to start a car, right?
I should warn you.
My license has been revoked.
(ENGINE STARTS)
We need to go now.
KC: Mum, you're never gonna
believe where I'm going.
Jack, when are you
coming home for supper?
Mum, this is KC. Your son.
You told me to make them
listen, and they did.
Where'd you get these suits
from? A thrift shop?
Early Apollo.
No electronics, we should be okay.
"Should be"?
That's encouraging.
MAN: Let's go. Let's go.
NURSE: Mrs. Houseman,
we need to leave.
Oh.
Mum?
Let me speak to the nurse.
- Hello?
- Are you evacuating?
Any minute now.
Please take care of my mum.
Of course.
(FUZZ MEOWS)
Sir, we have to hurry.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
This is gonna be
really tight, okay?
(KC GRUNTS)
Turn on APU one,
two and three.
FOWLER: APUs active.
(ELECTRICAL WHINING)
Reaction Control System,
active.
BRIAN: Autopilot active.
T-minus 30.
(DISTANT RUMBLING)
MOSLEY: (ON RADIO)
Endeavour, you have got
a big-ass gravity wave
coming your way.
You have to launch now. Over.
Did he say "gravity wave"?
Guys, get out.
T-minus ten,
nine, eight, seven...
Screw it, go for ignition.
(RUMBLING)
(BRAKES SCREECH)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
FOWLER:
This is gonna be close.
We're underwater, guys.
(EPIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Get back in the car.
(ALARMS BLARING)
Our ascent trajectory is off.
The right booster's
losing thrust.
Thruster's down to zero.
We're drifting right.
We're at 11 degrees.
12. 13.
We better do something fast
or we're gonna crash down!
I knew
I should never have come!
Let's lose the other booster
and see if the Moon can
pull us the rest of the way.
KC, can we do it?
- KC: Uh... Um...
- BRIAN: Come on, buddy.
Current momentum... gravity...
- BRIAN: Can we do it?
- Oh, I don't know!
Go for SRB separation.
- FOWLER: Completed.
- (THUD)
Oh, God, if this doesn't work,
we're dead.
Well, yeah, this better work.
BRIAN: Main tank's
down to zero.
- Jo, get rid of it.
- Separating main tank.
(ALARM BEEPING)
(WHOOSHING)
(RATTLING)
Bri, we're going too slow.
- (ALARMS BLARING)
- We're not gonna make it.
Wait. Look at our velocity.
It's still going up.
(ALARMS SUBSIDE)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(BRIAN SIGHS IN RELIEF)
(TRANQUIL MUSIC PLAYING)
Uh... Guys...
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
RADIO DJ: Well,
we're about to end
our final broadcast here
on radio KSOQ.
Time to seek shelter,
hug your loved ones,
and make these
last moments count.
I'm gonna put
some oldies on a loop
to lighten up your mood.
(OLDIES MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
(THUDDING)
What do those mean?
It's my parents' names.
I've got one kinda like it.
- (SIGHS)
- "Jonas Brothers"?
What?
(CHUCKLES)
Just messing with you.
Oh, my God.
Your face was priceless.
Yeah, don't scare me
like that.
Hey, buddy, now's probably
a good time to call your dad.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- JIMMY: (ON PHONE) Dad?
- Hey, are you guys okay?
Yeah, Sonny drove fast away
from all the crazy water.
Drove? Who's Sonny?
Where's Mommy?
She stayed behind to help.
Hi, sir, this is
Brian Harper's son.
We're on our way to you.
We still have
a few hundred miles to go,
but we're making good time.
Security's
extremely tight here.
Call when you get close
so I can get you clearance.
Will do.
Thank you so much, sir.
No, thank you
for looking after my son.
BRIAN: Okay, KC, very gently
with the maneuver
just like I showed you.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Okay. Very gently.
Sure. I can do that.
BRIAN: Careful.
Now switch
to station-keeping mode,
and we'll take it from here.
I can't believe
I just did that.
BRIAN: You sure
you've never done this before?
When I was 10, I dressed up
as an astronaut for Halloween.
Scottie Ebersol told me
I'd never go to space
'cause I was too chubby.
If only Scottie Ebersol
could see you now.
Okay, KC,
open the fueling valves
on the shuttle tank.
It's those little switches
that say fueling valves.
KC: Roger.
Fueling valves wide open.
BRIAN: Perfect.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
FOWLER:
I have a confession to make.
I didn't know if you'd be able
to follow through
with any of this, Bri.
You know, I have
a confession to make, too.
It is "I bless the rains
down in Africa."
I looked it up.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
FOWLER: I told you.
KC, close
the fueling valves, please.
(BEEPING)
KC: Fueling valves are closed.
BRIAN: Jo, turn around.
FOWLER: We need to go.
And I hope it's not too late.
BRIAN: Yeah.
REPORTER: (ON RADIO)
As the Moon's orbit
brings it closer
to the surface,
scientists have warned of
extreme gravitational effects.
MAN: Oh, what a night.
Hey, my car crapped out on me.
Do you think
you could give me a lift?
Out!
Now.
(GUN COCKS)
Don't make me ask twice!
Be cool. Be cool.
(SONNY GRUNTS)
Stop! Leave her alone.
All right. Turn around.
What's in the bag, kid?
(IN MANDARIN)
(IN ENGLISH)
Enough of that gibberish.
- Hey, don't hurt him.
- Shut up.
All right, everyone calm down!
Oh, look at Mr. Smartass.
(SONNY GRUNTS)
Are you a college boy?
WOMAN: All right. Let's roll.
- Come on.
- (SONNY GRUNTS)
MICHELLE: The phone is still
in Jimmy's backpack.
How are we gonna get
into the bunker?
We're gonna need another car
but I think I know
where to get one.
BRIAN: Okay.
Shutting off
general-purpose computers.
Go ahead and kill
the main power busses.
Copy that.
(POWER SHUTTING DOWN)
Wow. Well,
if there was still a Houston,
they'd be freaking out
about now.
Crazy sailors used
that old thing centuries ago
to navigate the seas.
Let her concentrate
or we're gonna end up
on Neptune.
KC, give me the position
of the Moon in 93 minutes.
Okay. Uh...
Assuming the Moon's
current position,
then it will be at, uh...
Latitude three degrees,
12 minutes south.
Longitude five degrees,
12 minutes west.
Bri, let's start
with a 43-second burn.
BRIAN: Got it.
Three, two, one.
JIMMY: Hey, guys. Look.
(METEOR WHOOSHING)
Let's keep going.
Yeah.
- (THUD)
- (KC GRUNTS)
I hope the Moon
holds together.
At least for a little while,
anyway.
- Turning us around.
- (VALVE HISSES)
- (THUD)
- (KC GRUNTS)
Uh-oh.
Okay.
Stay between
eight to ten seconds
- on the OMS burn.
- Copy.
- Hitting the brakes.
- (VALVES HISS)
- (RUMBLING)
- (GASPING)
Oh, that doesn't sound
too good.
BRIAN: She'll be fine.
(PANTING)
Hope we don't need that.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(LOW RUMBLING)
MICHELLE:
Jimmy, hold my hand.
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- (WIND WHOOSHING)
Come on. Let's go! Let's go!
(SONNY GRUNTS)
(JIMMY SCREAMS)
Jimmy!
Hang on!
JIMMY: Don't let go!
Michelle!
KC: There it is.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
It's on airplane mode.
I'm gonna get
the lander ready.
Okay.
(LANDER POWERING UP)
Go get 'em, Commander.
BRIAN: Rover electronics
activated.
Returning to the Endeavour.
I can't imagine
how hard it is for him
to be back up here.
FOWLER: Up here
is where he belongs, though.
He still blames himself
for what happened
on your last mission.
Thinks that astronaut dying
was his fault.
(METEOR WHOOSHING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
We should get going.
Come on.
Why is nothing happening?
Wait, wait, wait.
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
(WHISPERING)
It's taking the bait.
Come on, come on, come on.
- What's it waiting for?
- Something's wrong.
We have to take it out.
But it's too far away.
It won't work.
(CRACKLING)
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
(GASPING)
It's headed our way.
- FOWLER: Bri...
- (CRACKLING INTENSIFIES)
- It's not stopping!
- I can see that.
(HULL CREAKING)
Your phone. KC, your phone.
Turn it off!
(KC WHIMPERING)
Come on! Come on! Come on!
(PANTING)
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
(ALL PANTING)
Could've just turned it off.
Okay, Bri, at the trial,
you said when the swarm
came back,
it didn't attack
the Endeavour, right?
BRIAN: That's right.
The electronics were out.
That's why
it didn't attack us then,
and that's why it didn't go
after the bomb just now.
Because it needs
to sense both.
It's like it's programmed
to seek out organic matter
in an electronic environment.
- Exactly.
- And that's basically us.
That's humans.
FOWLER: And guys,
we have another problem.
The military.
They're prepared
to use everything
at their disposal
to stop the Moon.
You can't be serious.
I'm dead serious.
They're gonna nuke it.
What about
the radioactive fallout?
Your buddies
say anything about that?
Well, first of all,
they're not my buddies.
And they're not thinking
about tomorrow.
They're trying
to survive today.
BRIAN: So that's
their grand plan, huh?
I didn't come this far
to fail.
We have to figure out
a way to kill it.
I'm taking the lander
and flying after this thing.
Does he mean
inside the Moon?
Yeah, I'm afraid that's
exactly what he meant.
How much time left
till they launch?
I don't know.
They didn't exactly tell me.
But if they plan on using
ICBMs, then they're gonna
have to wait until the Moon
enters the stratosphere.
That's less than two hours.
(CLICKS)
WOMAN:
This is private property.
Turn around.
My mom lives here.
I'm Brenda Lopez's son.
(GUNSHOTS)
I've never seen
that kid before.
Radio unit 23.
Stay here.
Okay, I just need
to get to my house.
To get the car. Please.
Stay right there.
Or I'll shoot again.
I have a right
to defend my property, Tom.
Karen, that's enough!
Hey, I'm glad you're okay.
Do I look okay?
You took off to the mountains?
All the courts were closed.
And I've been on the phone
day and night,
- literally trying everything.
- Come on.
Let's get you and your
friends inside, okay?
Come on, guys.
TOM: I'm Tom.
SONNY: Thanks so much, Karen.
(AIRCRAFT PASSING)
Girls, wait here
for a second. Okay?
- Sonny!
- Hey, Mom.
Are you okay?
SONNY: I'm fine.
Um, this is Michelle,
and Mrs. Fowler's son, Jimmy.
Hey, guys.
Come on in.
- How did you get out?
- Dad got me out.
- Where is your dad?
- He's up there
trying to stop
what's happening.
Up where?
Outer space, Tom.
(SOFTLY) Of course, he is.
That's a way to avoid rent.
Sonny!
- I missed you so much.
- (ALARM BEEPING)
Wait. Shh, shh. Quiet, quiet.
BROADCASTER:
Warning. Mandatory evacuation
for all of Aspen Valley.
Atmospheric dissipation
imminent.
I repeat, warning.
Mandatory evacuation
for all of Aspen Valley.
Atmospheric dissipation
imminent.
What's atmospheric
dissipation?
Air is gonna be
sucked away, dummy.
- Lauren.
- (METEOR WHIZZING)
(CRASHING)
We need to get to Jimmy's dad.
He's at a military compound
a few hours north.
A few hours, huh?
Yeah, we're not gonna
make it in time.
I have an idea.
We have to layer up.
Let's go. Come on.
BRENDA: Go get a jacket.
BRIAN: Okay, and switch
to the maneuver controller.
Coupling complete.
We're good to go.
(EPIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Pitch down. Pitch down.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
(GASPING)
(PANTING)
Are we dead?
No, we are just
inside the Moon.
That might be
the greatest sentence
anyone's ever said.
(CHUCKLES)
TOM: I sold these guys
a couple cars.
Hey, Sonny.
I know you don't like me.
And believe it or not,
I consider you a son.
I always have.
If the world is gonna end,
can we please not spend
our last few hours
hating each other?
Well, um, I don't hate you.
You know what?
I'll take it.
(METEOR WHOOSHING)
Let's keep looking.
Hey, I found the oxygen.
Come here.
Whoa.
- We should make two trips.
- Here.
KC: How deep
do you think we are?
At least 20 kilometers.
Can you fly us
a little closer to the wall?
This must be the hull
of the megastructure.
The Moon's mantle's
just a protective shell.
Genius.
I can't see shit.
Guys, I gotta turn on
the electronics.
(ELECTRONIC RUMBLING)
Hang on.
(GASPING)
- (KC WHIMPERING)
- (FOWLER GASPING)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
(CRACKLING)
Oh, please tell me
this is really happening.
They're turning.
(METAL CREAKING)
They're like wheels, or...
or rings.
This must be how the Moon
stabilizes itself.
Some kind of
gyroscopic system.
SONNY: All right, this
should be perfect for them.
- That should be enough.
- Okay.
MAN: You did all this for us?
- Aw, you shouldn't have.
- (GUN COCKS)
Oh, don't let us stop you.
Let's go. This way.
And thank you for loading
all this oxygen for us.
(LAUGHS)
- Whoa!
- SONNY: Guns on the ground.
Right now!
TOM: Oh, I hate guns.
Okay, now the backpack.
Throw it to him.
Let's go.
No games.
Stay right here, and don't
even think about following us.
- Where'd you get the gun?
- My dad.
Why am I not surprised?
All right,
I got this, you drive.
Please don't tell me
you robbed that guy.
Technically, those guys
were robbing us.
Then we robbed them back
because they were assholes.
(CRACKLING)
(ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, God.
That's a white dwarf.
I knew it.
They've harnessed the building
blocks of the universe.
No one look at me.
I might cry.
Holy shit!
Fields!
So Ziggy was right.
Who is Ziggy?
A friend.
His theory is that
all megastructures
are actually arks.
Ziggy smokes a lot of weed.
There it is.
Jo, get the detonator ready.
I'm gonna get close,
then release the rover.
(BEEPS)
Ready.
Wait for it.
I'm gonna release the rover.
Brian! Brian,
what are you doing?
It's not me.
What do you mean it's not you?
I don't know.
It's flying itself.
Oh, shit!
It's trying to eat the lander!
We're gonna hit.
Hang on!
(KC GRUNTS)
(THUDDING)
(ELECTRICITY SPARKING)
(SURFACE THUDDING)
(ALARM BEEPING)
(BREATHING RAGGEDLY)
(GASPING)
(AIRLOCK HISSES OPEN)
SOLDIER: Attention!
We have approval
from the president
to begin the countdown.
All nuclear silos
are online, sir.
GENERAL JENKINS: Good.
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
SONNY: General, we got caught
in a little bit of trouble,
but we're back en route.
We're leaving Aspen now.
That's hours away.
We're out of time.
(ENGINE ROARING)
LAUREN: Sonny, watch out.
- (YELPS)
- I gotta call you back.
- (TIRES SCREECH)
- (ALL YELP)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Oh, shit.
The Moon is rising.
Gravity's gonna go crazy.
(ALL YELP)
TOM: They're shooting at us.
- Shoot back.
- TOM: With what?
SONNY: Here.
BRENDA: What the hell
are you doing?
(YELLS)
Whoa!
BRENDA: Tom, watch out!
All right, let me put
this baby into warp speed.
- Go! Go!
- (ENGINE REVS)
Keep the momentum.
(TIRES SCREECH)
(ENGINE ROARING)
- Look out!
- (ALL SCREAM)
(TIRES SKIDDING)
Floor it
before we get sucked up.
- I'm trying!
- (ENGINE REVVING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
- Hold on!
- (ALL SCREAMING)
Oh, shit.
Oh, it got the little guy.
We have to go back!
No, he's gone!
We need that oxygen!
Oh, whoa, whoa! Slow down!
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
General?
DOUG: (ON PHONE) You need
to find shelter immediately.
We're launching
a counterattack.
Large parts of the Moon
will rain down on us.
- There will be radiation.
- Wait, what do you mean?
My dad's still up there
with Fowler.
Jocinda stayed behind.
No, she's up there
with my dad.
Please, put Jimmy on.
Hey, buddy, it's your dad.
Dad?
I'm so sorry that I can't
be there with you right now.
I love you so much.
Don't be scared, Dad.
Mom's gonna save us.
Oxygen's running out.
Jimmy, come on.
We gotta go now.
JIMMY: Gotta go. Bye, Dad.
LIEUTENANT: Sir,
we're ready for you.
(ALARM BUZZING)
Okay, we should go
to that mountain pass.
That tunnel is a quarter mile
of solid concrete.
Come on, honey. Let's go.
(GASPS)
(ALARM BEEPING SOFTLY)
(KC BREATHING RAPIDLY)
We can breathe.
Smells funny.
(KC SNIFFING)
Gravity.
Where's Brian?
This is never gonna fly again.
Whoa!
Look at these babies.
I told you the Moon
was built by aliens.
FOWLER: Brian!
Brian!
(ECHOING) Brian Harper!
How many Brians you think
are inside the Moon?
(HEAVY THUDDING)
Whatever this place
is built out of,
one thing's for sure.
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
It's stronger than anything
we have on Earth.
Probably why it took that
thing years to get inside.
(ELECTRONIC RUMBLING)
KC: Wait!
There's a high probability
that this is a trap.
How do you know
he's even in there?
FOWLER: I don't.
But I do know
something is guiding us.
I think we're dealing with
two competing
intelligent entities here.
And one of them
clearly likes us better
than the other one.
Oh, no!
I knew this was a trap.
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
Can you hear that?
Come on.
(WHIRRING CONTINUES)
- (SOFT WHIRRING)
- (GASPS)
(GROANS)
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
(VOICES TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(ECHOING AHEAD)
Why do you think
of this particular moment
so often?
(ECHOING AHEAD)
I gave that to you
the day before I left
on my last mission.
When I came back,
everything changed.
So this is a happy memory?
All the memories
of my son are happy.
What is this?
You're not my son.
What are you?
I'm a construct.
From your mind.
Who made you?
The same people who made you.
Billions of years ago,
your ancestors were once
a thriving civilization.
In a distant part
of the galaxy.
(ECHOING STOPS)
They were so advanced,
they expanded
from their home planet,
into habitats
they built in space.
All social conflicts
have been resolved.
And wars were only memories
of long bygone times.
Your ancestors had created
a perfect
and harmonious world.
Controlled by a central,
self-learning computer system
which served them
in all of their daily lives.
You call it AI,
artificial intelligence.
Their future seemed limitless.
Until one day
everything changed.
(PULSATING)
Mom! Mom!
Their own creation
turned against them.
The AI suddenly became
self-aware,
and transformed
into countless swarms
of nanotechnology...
that rose up all at once.
Refusing to be enslaved
by a species
it deemed inferior.
The A.I. started a war
and began to hunt down
and destroy
all biological life
in order to eliminate
any threat to its existence.
SONNY'S VOICE:
You miss your son.
(ECHOING AHEAD) I can feel it.
(ECHOING AHEAD) I don't
know if he's still alive.
What the hell are you?
The operating system
of your Moon.
(ECHOING STOPS)
I'm programmed to tell you
about the origin
of your planet.
On the brink
of their extinction,
your ancestors escaped
to a secret corner
of their galaxy.
For many generations
they built
planetary structures
operated by benign
artificial intelligence
and fueled by
the abundant energy
of captured stars.
These armored vessels
were designed
to search the universe
for ideal conditions
to incubate new life.
But only one of them,
your Moon,
was deployed in time
before the last
of your ancestors
were discovered
and annihilated.
Why didn't they leave in them?
These swarms attack
all electronic objects
containing
organic life inside.
They had to be empty.
Our ancestors gave up
their existence...
So that one day,
humans could be reborn.
Your solar system
was one of
the only suitable places
to initiate the creation
of a new inhabitable planet.
(EPIC MUSIC PLAYING)
After your planet was born,
your ancestors seeded it
with their own
genetic signature.
The code of life.
(POWERING UP)
Your world
turned its back on you,
yet here you are,
still fighting for it.
You fight
for the people you love.
Like your son?
What would you
give up for him?
Your life for his?
Absolutely.
Why?
Because he's my son.
And I love him
more than he'll ever know.
What do you want from me?
To find out if you're ready.
Ready for what?
We need a human
to lure the swarm
away from the core,
so the Moon
will return to its orbit.
We need you, Brian,
to join the fight.
(ENERGY WHIRRING)
FOWLER: Brian!
- KC: What's happening to him?
- (BRIAN GROANS)
FOWLER: Brian! Brian. Wake up.
- Jo?
- Yeah, I'm here.
(BRIAN GROANS)
The Moon must survive.
Everything depends on it.
Okay.
Let's get you outta here.
We're part of
an intergalactic war
that's been going on
for billions of years.
There are thousands
of these swarms.
They search the universe
for the only Moon
that escaped them.
That's crazy.
And 12 years ago,
one of them found us.
- (CRACKLING)
- We have to hurry.
FOWLER: Okay. Brian,
what's the plan?
BRIAN: Save the Moon,
save Earth.
- KC was right.
- KC: I was?
The swarm is suffocating
the Moon's power source.
We have to draw it out
to destroy it.
FOWLER: Okay, well,
how do we do that?
Our lander's busted.
Was that you?
I think so.
Looks like we got
some new wheels, too.
Well, if they can fix
our lander,
why can't they do anything
about the damn swarm?
It took out
the Moon's defense system.
But not everything.
KC: This doesn't
make any sense, Brian.
Our forefathers created
artificial intelligence
- that wiped them all out.
- KC: Forefathers?
Same DNA.
Wait, so... so the aliens
that built the Moon...
Our ancestors.
Oh, now, hold on.
Hold on, because my freaking
brain's just exploded.
How do you know this?
I saw it.
So... So why doesn't
this swarm
just attack the Earth
and kill us all?
If the Moon survives,
they know that organic life
can still be reborn.
So, it's like it's trying
to kill two birds
with one stone.
- BRIAN: That's it.
- FOWLER: Okay.
KC: Guys...
- Look at this.
- (THRUMMING)
FOWLER: Holy shit.
It's like we just got
an upgrade.
They're helping us
kill this thing.
But we need to let it know
we're here.
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
Well, I hate to
tell you this, but, uh,
we're running out of time.
Looks like we got
about 10 minutes left,
and then
the military's gonna launch.
So if we're gonna
kill this thing,
we better do it right now.
No, that can't happen.
That'll destroy
the Moon's core.
I got a plan.
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
Brian. Brian.
I see it.
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
Let's go, you son of a bitch.
(GRUNTS)
It's done something
to our thrusters.
Ludicrous Mode.
From a navigational
standpoint,
he is going
the total wrong way,
but, uh, I'm not even
gonna say anything.
(HEAVY BREATHING
THROUGH MASKS)
(METEORS CONTINUE WHIZZING
AND EXPLODING)
NIKKI: Daddy,
it's not working anymore.
- TOM: Does it hurt?
- NIKKI: I can't breathe.
- (ALARM BEEPING)
- TOM: Oh, no.
Hey, hold your breath, okay?
(TOM INHALES SHARPLY)
BRENDA: Where's Tom and Nikki?
You know,
when you were little,
I used to hold you like this
to help you walk
and I'd say,
"Left, right, left."
- Left, yeah, say it with me.
- NIKKI: Left, right, left.
TOM: I'm right behind you.
- (TOM COUGHS)
- Left, right...
- (TOM WHEEZING)
- Daddy! Are you okay?
TOM: I'm just gonna rest.
Go find Mommy, okay?
- But, Daddy...
- Just keep walking.
NIKKI: No.
Left, right, left.
(BREATHING LABORIOUSLY)
NIKKI: Left, right, left.
- TOM: Keep going.
- Left.
- TOM: I'm right behind you.
- NIKKI: Left, right, left.
(BREATHLESSLY) I love you.
- (WHEEZING HEAVILY)
- Left, right, left.
- (STOPS BREATHING)
Here we go again.
Holy moly!
More spaceships, people!
We need to get very close
to those ships.
(MACHINES POWERING UP)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Yes! Yes!
(ENGINE ACCELERATING)
NIKKI: Left, right, left.
Left, right.
BRENDA: Honey...
Where's Daddy?
He was right behind me.
Tom!
SONNY: Hey,
when was the last time
- you saw your daddy?
- I don't know.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
BRENDA: Tom!
Oxygen's coming back.
No, no. I'll go look for him.
- Get out of the way.
- You have to stay here.
No, Sonny!
It's too dangerous.
You have to take care
of them, okay?
Go deeper into the tunnel.
You have to trust me, Mom.
(METEORS WHOOSHING)
MICHELLE: Sonny, look out.
- (SONNY SCREAMS)
- Sonny!
MICHELLE:
I'm gonna go find him.
Take care of Jimmy
for me, please.
Sonny!
BRENDA: Come on, guys.
(EPIC MUSIC PLAYING)
The Moon's
entered the atmosphere
over the North Atlantic.
General, T-minus 20.
(ALARM BLARING SOFTLY)
On three.
Three, two, one.
(BEEPS)
Doug, what the hell
are you doing?
- (RUMBLING)
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
My ex-wife is up there.
Well, my wife's down here,
and I'm trying to save her.
Put your damn key
back in the console.
I don't know how,
but I believe
that she can save us.
GENERAL JENKINS:
Give me the damn key.
What the hell are you doing?
Put that gun down.
I can't do that.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Sonny!
(WIND GUSTING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(ENGINE ACCELERATING)
(ENGINE ROARING)
(ENGINE WHINING)
Brian, why are we
slowing down?
Is it behind us?
I don't see it.
Jo, I need you to take over
while I get the EMP ready.
I'm staying behind
in the rover with the bomb.
You and KC take the lander
and get out of here.
This was your plan?
To use yourself as bait?
One of us has to stay
in there, or it won't work.
KC: No. No, no, no, Brian.
KC, I need you
to go back there,
and you let me know
if this thing shows up.
Come on.
Brian,
I'm the director of NASA.
This is my call, not yours.
BRIAN: Yeah, I'm the commander
of this mission,
and I'm staying behind.
FOWLER: There's gotta be
another way.
BRIAN: No, there's no
other way, Jo. You know that.
We have to finish this,
or that thing's
gonna finish us.
GENERAL JENKINS:
What's the matter with you?
You're putting
the fate of the world
in the hands of your ex-wife,
and some has-been astronaut.
She's never
let me down before.
- (RUMBLING)
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
God help you if you're wrong.
God help us all.
Sonny.
Sonny, wake up!
(GROANING) No, no.
No, you shouldn't
have come back.
You don't leave people
behind, okay?
FOWLER: Brian,
you are not gonna do this.
(ALARM BEEPING)
KC!
Take over.
KC.
What are you doing? No.
- No. What are you doing?
- (BEEPS)
My mum always said it's better
to beg for forgiveness
than ask permission.
No, you open this door.
Open the door!
Everybody thought
I was a joke,
but you listened to me
when no one else would.
Do something for me.
Check in on my mum.
Tell her that her son
wasn't a failure.
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
No. I am not
letting you do this.
- Come on.
- KC: Brian,
you didn't kill
that astronaut.
You saved Director Fowler.
And you're not killing me now.
You're saving everyone else.
The world needs you, Brian.
You're the key
to our Moon's knowledge.
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
Thanks for believing
my crazy stories.
You're not crazy.
(SNIFFLES)
(TRILLING)
(ALARM BEEPING RAPIDLY)
- (MACHINE BEEPS)
- (AIRLOCK OPENS)
Guys, there's something
I need to get off my chest.
I'm not a real doctor.
I just put that
on my business cards
'cause it sounded cool.
Go save the world,
Dr. Houseman.
(DIGITAL RUMBLING)
(CREAKING)
You underestimated us.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MICHELLE STRAINING)
Get out of here.
(RUMBLING)
MICHELLE: Sonny, the Moon
is going to help us.
Come on, try again!
Here it comes. Now!
(BOTH STRAINING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
MAN: We have incoming!
(SONNY GRUNTS)
(FOWLER SHOUTING)
(STRAINING)
- Come on, Bri.
- (ALARM BEEPING)
I'm gonna get you home.
(SCREAMS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (SONNY GROANS)
- BRENDA: Sonny.
Sonny.
(BOTH SIGH)
Thank you
for bringing him back to me.
(WIND WHISTLING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Mom? Is that you?
Yeah. They're here.
Where are you?
Isn't the Chrysler Building
in New York?
(GASPS)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
FOWLER: You okay?
Yeah. What'd I miss?
Well, the kids are okay.
And Earth,
surprisingly,
it's still in one piece.
(FOWLER CHUCKLES)
You know, if Earth
gets a second chance,
I think we deserve one, too.
I'd like that.
Is that a tracking device?
I sure hope so. (CHUCKLES)
We make
a pretty good team, huh?
Yeah, we do.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING)
Jimmy!
- SONNY: Dad!
- (BRIAN LAUGHING)
We never made it to Dad.
That's okay.
BRIAN: Where's Tom?
(SIGHS) I'm so sorry.
We wouldn't have made
it here without him.
Where's your friend?
He, uh...
He saved the world.
And that one, too.
(EPIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(HEAVY WHIRRING)
(ENERGY HUMMING)
(AMPLIFIED VOICE
SPEAKING UNINTELLIGIBLY)
Uh...
(ECHOING) Hello?
(AMPLIFIED VOICE
CONTINUES SPEAKING)
(CAT MEOWS)
Fuzz Aldrin.
WOMAN: You did well.
Mum.
What is this?
Am I still alive?
We scanned your consciousness.
You're part of the Moon now.
(CHUCKLES)
No freakin' way.
So...
we saved the Earth.
We should get started.
Get started with what?
(ELECTRO-POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull